

# kierra palmer

#### COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

## profile

My name is Kierra and I am currently a Junior at Weber State University. My major is Computer Science with a minor in Web Technologies. My goal in the next two years is to finish my studies at WSU and hopefully get an internship or job to help expand my knowledge in the technologies world. My most defining qualities include my strong determination to succeed and my unique perspective on topics of interest.

#### contact

208-317-9910 **Phone** 

**Email** kierrapalmer@aol.com

icarus.cs.weber.edu/~kp63421/index.html Website

Ogden, UT Location

## education

Weber State University • Aug 2015-current

Cumulative GPA: 3.91 Major: Computer Science

Boise High School • Aug 2012-May 2015

Weighted GPA: 4.18 **Graduated with Honors** 

### skills

- Critical Thinking
- Problem Solving
- Multitasking
- Motivation Honesty
- C++ and Java
- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript/JQuery
- Oracle
- Photoshop/InDesign

## experience

Weber State University . Student Aid Aug 2016-current

Assist in computer science office with any secretarial tasks needed, including but not limited to: copying, filing, creating word and excel documents, and creating event flyers

Weber State University • Testing Proctor Jan 2016-Apr 2016

Check in students and ensure that they have the necessary tools for their test. Proctor students throughout their tests.

Monitor open computer lab and assist with any printing or computer questions.

Taffy Treasures • Cashier & Graphic Designer Feb 2015 - Mar 2016

Greet customers and assist them with their purchases. Manage all social media accounts and create documents and promotional posters for all store sales and events

# leaderhsip/involvement

WSU Association of Computing Machinery President • 2017-current

Plan and lead monthly group meetings and/or parties Coordinate with advisor and vice-president to bring in monthly speakers on computing related topics

WSU Residence Hall Association Director of Marketing • 2016-17

Assist in representing students who live in WSU Housing. Additionally, I ran the social media accounts and created event flyers when needed